// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The head of which animal is front and center in an infamous scene from The Godfather?",
    answer: "Horse",
    options: [
      "Tiger",
      "Horse",
      "Lion",
      "Dog"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Sean Connery won his oscar starring in what film? ",
    answer: "The Untouchables",
    options: [
      "Dr. No",
      "The Rock",
      "The Untouchables",
      "The Hunt For Red October"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What Hollywood movie star plays himself in the movie Zombieland?",
    answer: "Bill Murray",
    options: [
      "George Clooney",
      "Johnny Depp",
      "Ben Stiller",
      "Bill Murray"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What was Quentin Tarantino's first feature as writer/director?",
    answer: "Reservoir Dogs",
    options: [
      "Reservoir Dogs",
      "Pulp Fiction",
      "Kill Bill",
      "The Hateful Eight"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which movie star is killed off in the opening scene of Scream?",
    answer: "Drew Barrymore",
    options: [
      "Drew Barrymore",
      "Nicole Kidman",
      "Liv Tyler",
      "Neve Campbell"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What Martin Scorsese movie holds the all time record for F bombs?",
    answer: "The Wolf of Wall Street",
    options: [
      "GoodFellas",
      "Casino",
      "The Wolf of Wall Street",
      "The Departed"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In 1994 romcom Four Weddings and a Funeral, Who s funeral does the group attend?",
    answer: "Gareth",
    options: [
      "Matthew",
      "Tom",
      "Bernard",
      "Gareth"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who replaced Richard Harris as Dumbledore in the Harry Potter movies?",
    answer: "Michael Gambon",
    options: [
      "Alan Rickman",
      "Michael Gambon",
      "Michael Caine",
      "Billy Connoly"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In which film does Winona Ryder play a characher called Kim Boggs?",
    answer: "Edward Scissorhands",
    options: [
      "Beetlejuice",
      "Mr.Deeds",
      "Little Woman",
      "Edward Scissorhands"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb:10,
    question: "Which furry species lives on the forest moon of Endor?",
    answer: "Ewoks",
    options: [
      "Ewoks",
      "Gremlins",
      "Pokemon",
      "Vulcans"
    ]
  },
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];